	[
		{
			"question": "This formation of Imperial Guard comes from he nuclear wartorn planet of Krieg. They specialize in mining operations and siege warfare.",
			"answer": "The Death Korp"
		}, {
			"question": "This formation of Imperial Guard comes from the extremely poor planet of Mordia. They are known for their well kept uniforms and executing orders to the letter until new orders are given",
			"answer": "Iron Guard"
		}, {
			"question": "This formation of Imperial Guard comes from a fortress world near the Eye of Terror. During the 13th Black Crusade, a saying came about, 'the planet broke before the guard did'.",
			"answer": "Cadian Guard"
		}, {
			"question": "This space marine legion is known for its unparalleled subterfuge operations. They can infiltrate almost any stronghold.",
			"answer": "Alpha"
		}, {
			"question": "This space marine legion that is masterful at siege warfare both in defense of a siege and attacking fortification.",
			"answer": "Imperial Fists"
		}, {
			"question": "This is the primarch of the Imperial Fist legion. He is mostly known for his level headedness and his orginization of the Imperial palace's defenses.",
			"answer": "Rogal Dorn"
		}, {
			"question": "This is the planet where the archtraitor Horus plotted the near total annahilation of multiple loyalist legions",
			"answer": "Istvaan V"
		},{
			"question":"This is the primarch of the Salamandar legion. He is known for his characterized by is caring of civilian populations.",
			"answer":"Vulkan"
		},{
			"question":"This is the name of the Chaos god of blood. He cares not form whence the blood flows... only that it flows",
			"answer":"Khorne"
		},{
			"question":"This is the Chaos god of change, magic and conspiracy.",
			"answer":"Tzeentch"
		},{
			"question":"This is Chaos god of stagnation, death and disease.",
			"answer":"Nurgle"
		},{
			"question":"This is the Chaos god of pleasure and pain. Nicknamed 'The Prince'",
			"answer":"Slaanesh"
		},{
			"question":"The is the fortress monastery of the Imperial Fists.",
			"answer": "Phalanx"
		},{
			"question":"This is space marine legion that is often called 'The Ultra-Smurfs'.",
			"answer": "Ultramarines"
		},{
			"question":"This space marine legion is known for being masters of hit and run tactics",
			"answer":"The White Scars"
		},{
			"question":"This space marine legion is known for mutation that sometimes causes members to mutate wolf like features",
			"answer":"Space Wolves"
		},{
			"question":"This is the primarch of the Space Wolves. He is known for as the 'Emperor`s executioner",
			"answer":"Leman Russ"
		},{
			"question":"Dis be da cula dat makz uz go fast!",
			"answer":"Red"
		},{
			"question":"W'en uz feelin' dat uz wantz to use dakka or choppa uz say dis.",
			"answer":"WAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAGH"
		},{
			"question":"Has u se'n a ork dis cula? Nough said!",
			"answer":"Purple"
		},{
			"question":"This is the city of the Dark Eldar (dark space elves)",
			"answer":"Commorragh"
		},{
			"question":"This is the place where Ynnari usually live.",
			"answer":"Craftworld"
		},{
			"question":"This is the company that produces Warhammer 40k merchandise",
			"answer":"Games Workshop"
		},{
			"question":"This is the company that makes extremely expensive resin models, some of which are for 40K",
			"answer":"Forge World"
		},{
			"question":"This is the company that publishes Warhammer 40K books",
			"answer":"Black Library"
		}
	]
